<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Introduction on Jellyfish Jabberings</title>
    <link>http://jellyfishjabberings.ssaraf.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Introduction on Jellyfish Jabberings</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="http://jellyfishjabberings.ssaraf.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://jellyfishjabberings.ssaraf.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jellyfishjabberings.ssaraf.com/about/</guid>
      <description>About this site # I&amp;rsquo;m nearing my 4 year anniversary at Benchling and, in the tradition of an undergraduate thesis at the end of college, I thought it&amp;rsquo;d be worth writing up all of my learnings in a place where others can read them.
The target audience for this is current Benchlings and ex-Benchlings, though there&amp;rsquo;s nothing company-sensitive or non-public on this site.
What is your goal in writing this?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Organizational memory is very short</title>
      <link>http://jellyfishjabberings.ssaraf.com/essays/memory/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jellyfishjabberings.ssaraf.com/essays/memory/</guid>
      <description>Organizational memory is very short # Median tenure at a tech company is about 2.5 years, and getting shorter. And while I think that&amp;rsquo;s generally good for employees, who can grow in their careers, compensation, and opportunities by switching roles frequently, it makes the companies themselves weaker.
The best people for the job # It took me a long time to realize that the smartest technologists, the people who really know what they&amp;rsquo;re doing, they don&amp;rsquo;t often write in a public facing way where other people can read it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Process over Speed is usually a mistake</title>
      <link>http://jellyfishjabberings.ssaraf.com/essays/process/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jellyfishjabberings.ssaraf.com/essays/process/</guid>
      <description>At me ipso nepotibus nunc celebratior genus # Tanto oblite # Lorem markdownum pectora novis patenti igne sua opus aurae feras materiaque illic demersit imago et aristas questaque posset. Vomit quoque suo inhaesuro clara. Esse cumque, per referri triste. Ut exponit solisque communis in tendens vincetis agisque iamque huic bene ante vetat omina Thebae rates. Aeacus servat admonitu concidit, ad resimas vultus et rugas vultu dignamque Siphnon.
Quam iugulum regia simulacra, plus meruit humo pecorumque haesit, ab discedunt dixit: ritu pharetramque.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Example draft</title>
      <link>http://jellyfishjabberings.ssaraf.com/essays/example/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jellyfishjabberings.ssaraf.com/essays/example/</guid>
      <description>What is this # Columns # Columns help organize shorter pieces of content horizontally for readability.
{{&amp;lt; columns &amp;gt;}} &amp;lt;!-- begin columns block --&amp;gt; # Left Content Lorem markdownum insigne... &amp;lt;---&amp;gt; &amp;lt;!-- magic separator, between columns --&amp;gt; # Mid Content Lorem markdownum insigne... &amp;lt;---&amp;gt; &amp;lt;!-- magic separator, between columns --&amp;gt; # Right Content Lorem markdownum insigne... {{&amp;lt; /columns &amp;gt;}} Buttons # Buttons are styled links that can lead to local page or external link.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
